Place the smartphone on counter
Open fridge
Take eggs
Take chives
Place eggs on fridge
Close fridge
Place eggs on counter
Place chives on counter
Take mug
Place mug on counter
Crack eggs
Crack egg
Take fork
Scramble eggs
Place fork on sink
Take pan
Turn down stove
Control heating stove
Rinse hands
Open cabinet
Take oil
Pour oil on pan
Open cabinet
Put oil on cabinet
Place eggs shells on bin
Take pan
Distribute oil
Take spactula
Take mug
Pour omelet on pan
Rinse mug
Open dishwasher
Pull tray
Put mug on dishwasher
Push tray
Close dishwasher
Take slicing tray
Take chives
Take knife
Slice chives
Open fridge
Take cheese
Close fridge
Cut cheese
Open fridge
Place cheese in fridge
Close fridge
Take a spatula
Flip omelet
Add chives to omelet
add cheese to omelet
rinse slicing table
take a spatula
fold omelet
cooking omelet
take a spatula and pan
flip omelet
turn off stove
take bowl
place bowl on counter
open cabinet
take porridge
Add porridge.
Place porridge in cabinet.
Close cabinet.
Add water.
Place bowl on counter.
Take spoon.
[END SUBTITLE]